https://atomicinsights.com/wpautoterms/privacy-policy/

Skip to primary navigation Skip to main content Skip to primary sidebarHome
Last updated: July 2, 2020
Atomic Insights (“us”, “we”, or “our”) operates the Atomic Insights website (the “Service”).
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information when you use our Service.
We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use your Personal Information for providing and improving the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible at https://atomicinsights.com
Information Collection And Use
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. Personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) may include, but is not limited to:
Name
Email address
Log Data
We collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive.
We use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Security
The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Links To Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 (“Children”).
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Information, please contact us. If we discover that a child under 18 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our servers immediately.
Compliance With Laws
We will disclose your Personal Information where required to do so by law or subpoena.
Changes To This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
November 2020  (6)
October 2020  (3)
September 2020  (1)
August 2020  (1)
July 2020  (3)
June 2020  (3)
May 2020  (5)
April 2020  (6)
March 2020  (5)
February 2020  (1)
October 2019  (2)
September 2019  (2)
August 2019  (1)
July 2019  (1)
April 2019  (2)
March 2019  (2)
February 2019  (4)
January 2019  (3)
November 2018  (1)
October 2018  (3)
September 2018  (3)
August 2018  (3)
July 2018  (4)
June 2018  (1)
May 2018  (1)
April 2018  (2)
March 2018  (2)
February 2018  (9)
January 2018  (5)
December 2017  (8)
November 2017  (10)
October 2017  (10)
September 2017  (3)
August 2017  (12)
July 2017  (7)
June 2017  (4)
May 2017  (10)
April 2017  (15)
March 2017  (14)
February 2017  (12)
January 2017  (17)
December 2016  (4)
November 2016  (12)
October 2016  (10)
September 2016  (3)
August 2016  (6)
July 2016  (11)
June 2016  (19)
May 2016  (19)
April 2016  (14)
March 2016  (13)
February 2016  (21)
January 2016  (21)
December 2015  (17)
November 2015  (9)
October 2015  (18)
September 2015  (19)
August 2015  (19)
July 2015  (11)
June 2015  (20)
May 2015  (5)
April 2015  (12)
March 2015  (21)
February 2015  (14)
January 2015  (11)
December 2014  (17)
November 2014  (17)
October 2014  (24)
September 2014  (14)
August 2014  (22)
July 2014  (10)
June 2014  (24)
May 2014  (15)
April 2014  (15)
March 2014  (30)
February 2014  (21)
January 2014  (34)
December 2013  (19)
November 2013  (28)
October 2013  (20)
September 2013  (17)
August 2013  (14)
July 2013  (21)
June 2013  (14)
May 2013  (16)
April 2013  (19)
March 2013  (26)
February 2013  (18)
January 2013  (25)
December 2012  (25)
November 2012  (21)
October 2012  (15)
September 2012  (10)
August 2012  (27)
July 2012  (21)
June 2012  (22)
May 2012  (23)
April 2012  (18)
March 2012  (16)
February 2012  (13)
January 2012  (22)
December 2011  (35)
November 2011  (20)
October 2011  (18)
September 2011  (29)
August 2011  (20)
July 2011  (24)
June 2011  (24)
May 2011  (22)
April 2011  (21)
March 2011  (38)
February 2011  (26)
January 2011  (25)
December 2010  (20)
November 2010  (19)
October 2010  (20)
September 2010  (31)
August 2010  (21)
July 2010  (30)
June 2010  (26)
May 2010  (39)
April 2010  (33)
March 2010  (25)
February 2010  (46)
January 2010  (35)
December 2009  (32)
November 2009  (31)
October 2009  (33)
September 2009  (32)
August 2009  (33)
July 2009  (23)
June 2009  (43)
May 2009  (29)
April 2009  (20)
March 2009  (36)
February 2009  (29)
January 2009  (30)
December 2008  (25)
November 2008  (37)
October 2008  (26)
September 2008  (36)
August 2008  (35)
July 2008  (24)
June 2008  (22)
May 2008  (22)
April 2008  (33)
March 2008  (30)
February 2008  (36)
January 2008  (33)
December 2007  (32)
November 2007  (28)
October 2007  (28)
September 2007  (24)
August 2007  (14)
July 2007  (19)
June 2007  (23)
May 2007  (21)
April 2007  (23)
March 2007  (27)
February 2007  (24)
January 2007  (25)
December 2006  (28)
November 2006  (36)
October 2006  (23)
September 2006  (33)
August 2006  (28)
July 2006  (26)
June 2006  (21)
May 2006  (27)
April 2006  (25)
March 2006  (27)
February 2006  (20)
January 2006  (27)
December 2005  (34)
November 2005  (48)
October 2005  (23)
September 2005  (7)
August 2005  (12)
July 2005  (29)
June 2005  (10)
May 2005  (3)
April 2005  (3)
March 2005  (4)
February 2005  (1)
November 2004  (1)
August 2004  (1)
June 2004  (1)
May 2004  (1)
November 2003  (2)
April 2002  (1)
February 2002  (1)
November 2001  (1)
October 2001  (1)
September 2001  (1)
July 2001  (1)
June 2001  (1)
May 2001  (3)
April 2001  (3)
March 2001  (3)
February 2001  (2)
January 2001  (3)
December 2000  (2)
November 2000  (2)
January 1997  (5)
November 1996  (7)
September 1996  (7)
August 1996  (7)
July 1996  (6)
June 1996  (6)
May 1996  (4)
April 1996  (6)
March 1996  (5)
February 1996  (4)
January 1996  (4)
December 1995  (6)
November 1995  (4)
October 1995  (4)
September 1995  (5)
August 1995  (5)
July 1995  (5)
June 1995  (5)
May 1995  (7)
April 1995  (6)
Terms and Conditions - Privacy Policy
